<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>HEHATE.US</title><link href="http://hehate.us/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://hehate.us/feeds/all.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://hehate.us/</id><updated>2014-03-26T00:00:00-04:00</updated><entry><title>This Is All Shenanigans</title><link href="http://hehate.us/posts/2014/03/This-Is-All-Shenanigans/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2014-03-26T00:00:00-04:00</updated><author><name>Cabs</name></author><id>tag:hehate.us,2014-03-26:posts/2014/03/This-Is-All-Shenanigans/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;MIAMI (AP) -- Heat forward Chris Bosh has a confession: Games at this time of year simply mean more to him than games in December.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not exactly shocking, of course.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But when so much hubbub surrounded the last game between Miami and Indiana way back on Dec. 18, Bosh wasn't necessarily buying into the supposed significance. After all, he figured, the season was basically only one-third over at that point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Heat and Pacers finally play again on Wednesday. And this time, Bosh knows the buzz is real.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I know everybody's trying to make the games important back in December," Bosh said. "Well, now they're important."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Eastern Conference race won't be decided on Wednesday night, but the pendulum is either going to swing toward Indiana moving considerably closer to the No. 1 seed or back toward the Heat and a chaotic, potentially down-to-the-wire finish. If the Pacers -- who have been alone atop the East standings since Nov. 4 -- win, they would move three games clear of Miami in the East race. If the Heat prevail, the teams will be tied in the loss column.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And given that these teams don't like each other, plus have faced each other in extremely hard-fought series in each of the past two postseasons, this probably won't seem like just another regular-season game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Everybody's getting what they want," Bosh said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Neither team is exactly rolling into this matchup. Both teams have lost seven of their last 12 games, meaning the Heat have missed plenty of chances to grab the No. 1 spot, and the Pacers have missed plenty of chances to wrap up home-court throughout the East playoffs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We're just not clicking," Pacers center Roy Hibbert said after his team lost at Chicago on Monday night. "And we should be clicking."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Heat beat Portland on Monday -- squandering a 17-point lead in the fourth quarter before doing so -- but that snapped a highly befuddling streak of missed Miami opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before Monday, the Pacers had lost six games in March. And every time, the Heat either lost on the same night or in their next game, meaning a half-dozen chances to tighten up the East race were squandered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"As many chances as we had, we kept playing with it, we were struggling, they were struggling, we had our chances," Bosh said. "We still have our chance with two showdowns with them."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;True, Wednesday's isn't even the last Heat-Pacers meeting of this regular season. The teams square off in Miami on April 11.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This, though, might be the one that ultimately decides the East. If Miami falls three games out now -- the Pacers will have only 10 games left after Wednesday -- that could get the Heat to start thinking about how to rest certain players before the postseason begins. With Dwyane Wade in and out of the lineup often this season, Miami has used 18 starting lineups; the Pacers have used only three.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wade hopes to play Wednesday. The Heat said he sat out Monday with an ankle issue; Wade clarified on Tuesday that it's actually a sore Achilles' tendon, but he was able to practice before the team flew to Indianapolis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He participated in Wednesday morning's shootaround, then iced his knees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Miami likely won't have Ray Allen, however. Allen did not attend Wednesday morning's shootaround, and coach Erik Spoelstra plans to spend the afternoon "thinking about" how to divvy up time with the second unit if Allen does not play.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the Heat can close the gap in the standings, that could be a springboard for the two-time defending champions, who face a slew of sub-.500 teams in the next couple weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"It's coming down to a photo finish," Bosh said. "We have a unique opportunity. No matter what's happened this whole season, we're within striking distance. It's here and it'll be a great playoff atmosphere. I can't wait."&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="first"></category><category term="Team"></category></entry><entry><title>Just Bout Dat Action</title><link href="http://hehate.us/posts/2014/03/Just-Bout-Dat-Action/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2014-03-09T00:00:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Cabs</name></author><id>tag:hehate.us,2014-03-09:posts/2014/03/Just-Bout-Dat-Action/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p class="images"&gt; &lt;img src="/images/hehateme.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;The inspiration for the name of the site
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is my first mock up our new site He Hate Us. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What are we doing here at He Hate Us (HHU for the rest of the post)?&lt;br /&gt;
Well, a couple of us who met at MIT doing Aerospace Engineering have kept in touch post graduation and decided that there's very little we care about more than sports, despite our current lines of work. Due to our backgrounds, we've naturally been particularly interested in the more analytical approaches to sports that have started to be a regular part of mainstream discussion. Since we talk about sports with each other all day we thought we could attempt to contribute to the sports community and thought our own site would be a good forum to do that. We recruited another one of our friends and hope to post interesting stuff about sports here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What are we going to talk about?&lt;br /&gt;
Anything that comes to mind really. We'll try and keep to sports but after spending formative intellectual years reading Bill Simmons we like the idea of throwing in pop culture references. Luckily, there's a major sport being played year round so we'll have ideas year round. We all seem to really care about roster construction and team management so we'll have a bias towards player acquistion and evaluation compared to other articles. I'll apologize now for admitted homerism that will drive some of our articles. A couple of us were born and raised in the county of Dade. The other is as Pittsburgh as it gets. We'll likely have other friends drop in and contribute because this is really a fun, passion project and anyway to expand what we're doing would please us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="images"&gt; &lt;img src="/images/ABrown_FinalPlay.png")&gt;&lt;br&gt;This would have gotten too much coverage on this site&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who are we?&lt;br /&gt;
Cabs - One of the aforementioned guys born and raised in Miami, I will root for any Miami team. The Dolphins and the Heat are easy bets but I have a Panthers jersey and align myself with Da U (The Marlins just exist in my memory at the moment). I went to MIT where I met George because I'm no good at doing homework. I sold out and chased the money in finance and now live in New York.&lt;br /&gt;
George - The other guy from MIT has stayed true to actually doing something worthwhile with what he learned and is still there working on his PHD in Nuclear Engineering. He is from Pittsburgh, so I hear more about the Pirates than I ever cared to. He also has strong familial ties to Penn State.&lt;br /&gt;
Fwank - Is also from Miami. This means we get to lament the perpetual mediocrity of the Miami Dolphins. As impressionable children, Dan Marino was the Dolphins QB and now our bar of QB acceptance is impossibly high. He is the only one of us who went to a school with a legitimate sports program (Florida) but he managed to pick up an MBA from Emory and is up in New York now in the finance industry as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That's us. We hope to entertain and maybe provide some brain food. And always, thanks for reading.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="first"></category><category term="Team"></category></entry></feed>